<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inspire on Budibase: Web App Builder - Build Your Web App With Speed</title>
    <link>https://www.budibase.com/categories/inspire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Inspire on Budibase: Web App Builder - Build Your Web App With Speed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed and owned by Budibase</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.budibase.com/categories/inspire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Recent Examples Of Modern Web Application Design (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/5-examples-of-web-application-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/5-examples-of-web-application-design/</guid>
      <description>Every once in a while, I&amp;rsquo;ll come across examples of web application design that really draw me in. I&amp;rsquo;ve listed these web applications below and ranked them from 5 - 1.
These web applications contain a beautiful mix of design, usability and creativity. They are masterpieces, and wonderful tokens of inspiration.
Huge amounts of time and thought have went into the design of these web applications and credit must go to the designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Micro SaaS Ideas You&#39;ll Want To Steal in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/micro-saas-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/micro-saas-ideas/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m often thinking of Micro SaaS ideas for my next project but most of the time they are either rubbish or I don&amp;rsquo;t have the capacity to pursue them.
Instead of throwing all the good ideas away, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share them with you - how thoughtful, right 😄.
This post is not a simple static list; created, posted, and forgotten about. I will revisit and update this list on a monthly basis, delivering you super-fresh ideas to feed your entrepreneurial hunger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3 components of co-founder validation</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/cofoundervalidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/cofoundervalidation/</guid>
      <description>When someone whom you respect, approaches you with a business proposal, you listen. When their idea passes your gut validation, you get excited. When their vision of how a business should operate aligns with your vision, you fall in love with the product instantly. Your future brightens 💥
Respect, idea validation, shared vision. The 3 components of cofounder validation.
Respect can be earned, but best when it&amp;rsquo;s natural. Natural respect is only possible through previous encounters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>