<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>api on Budibase | Build internal tools on your own infrastructure</title>
    <link>https://www.budibase.com/tags/api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in api on Budibase | Build internal tools on your own infrastructure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed and owned by Budibase</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.budibase.com/tags/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Budibase Webhooks | Use webhooks to enrich your Budibase applications</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/webhooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/webhooks/</guid>
      <description>Use webhooks to connect your application to other applications. With webhooks, you can pull data into Budibase, and push data out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build apps from start to finish with Budibase</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/budibase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/budibase/</guid>
      <description>Budibase has its own database which you can use to support your application. This allows you to build applications from start to finish, all within Budibase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CouchDB integration with Budibase | Data source for building business apps</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/couchdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/couchdb/</guid>
      <description>Budibase integrates with Apache CouchDB allowing you to use CouchDB as your data source for your applications. CouchDB is an open-source document-oriented NoSQL database, implemented in Erlang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSV integration with Budibase | Data source for building business apps</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/csv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/csv/</guid>
      <description>A Comma-separated values file is a delimited text file that uses a comma to separate values.
Easily upload data to Budibase using CSVs. When you upload your CSV, Budibase will recognise the column/field names. You then have the ability to change the data type of the column, and remove if you like, before uploading to Budibase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DynamoDB integration with Budibase | Data source for building business apps</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/dynamodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/dynamodb/</guid>
      <description>Budibase integrates with DynamoDB allowing you to use DynamoDB as your data source for your applications. DynamoDB is a fully managed proprietary NoSQL database service by Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elasticsearch integration with Budibase | Data source for building business apps</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/elasticsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/elasticsearch/</guid>
      <description>Use Elasticsearch as your data source for your Budibase applications. Elasticsearch is a fully distributed, RESTful search and analytics engine based on the Lucene library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integromat integration with Budibase | Connect your app to the world</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/integromat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/integromat/</guid>
      <description>Integrate with a number of external APIs using the Budibase Integromat integration. Integromat is a tool that helps you automate manual processes, without coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB integration with Budibase | Use MongoDB as your data source</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/mongodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/mongodb/</guid>
      <description>Use MongoDB as your data source for your Budibase applications. MongoDB is a cross-platform document-oriented database program. Classified as a NoSQL database program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MySQL integration with Budibase | Data source for building business apps</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/mysql/</guid>
      <description>Budibase integrates with MySQL allowing you to use MySQL as your data source for your applications. MySQL Database Service is a fully managed database service to deploy cloud-native applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PostgreSQL integration with Budibase | Use PostgreSQL as your data source</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/postgres/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/postgres/</guid>
      <description>Use PostgreSQL as your data source for your Budibase applications. PostgreSQL, also known as Postgres, is a free and open-source relational database management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S3 integration with Budibase | Use S3 as your data source</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/s3/</guid>
      <description>Use Amazon S3 as your data and object source for your Budibase applications. Amazon S3 provides object storage through a web service interface which is accessible at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airtable integration with Budibase | Data source for building web apps</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/airtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/airtable/</guid>
      <description>Budibase integrates with Airtable allowing you to use Airtable as your data source for your applications. Airtable is a cloud collaboration service headquartered in San Francisco. It was founded in 2012 by Howie Liu, Andrew Ofstad, and Emmett Nicholas. Airtable is a spreadsheet-database hybrid, with the features of a database but applied to a spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArangoDB integration with Budibase | Data source for building internal tools</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/arangodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/arangodb/</guid>
      <description>Budibase integrates with ArangoDB allowing you to use ArangoDB as your data source for your applications. ArangoDB is a free and open-source native multi-model database system developed by ArangoDB GmbH. The database system supports three data models with one database core and a unified query language AQL. The query language is declarative and allows the combination of different data access patterns in a single query.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean integration with Budibase | Self-host your Budibase apps with Digital Ocean</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/digitalocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/digitalocean/</guid>
      <description>You can self-host your Budibase applications using DigitalOcean. DigitalOcean provides developers cloud services that help to deploy and scale applications that run simultaneously on multiple computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker integration with Budibase | Self-host your Budibase apps with Docker</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/integration/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/integration/docker/</guid>
      <description>You can self-host your Budibase applications using Docker Compose. Docker is a set of platform as a service products that use OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers. Containers are isolated from one another and bundle their own software, libraries and configuration files; they can communicate with each other through well-defined channels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
