<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No code platform | Open Source | Custom Software | Budibase on Budibase - No code platform | Open Source | Custom Software</title>
    <link>https://www.budibase.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in No code platform | Open Source | Custom Software | Budibase on Budibase - No code platform | Open Source | Custom Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed and owned by Budibase</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.budibase.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is custom software development in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/custom-software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/custom-software-development/</guid>
      <description>The world is eating software. 🌎 🍴🌐
The above is a tongue-in-cheek response to the famous words of Marc Andreessen, &amp;lsquo;software is eating the world.&amp;rsquo; Marc&amp;rsquo;s words hail from his wondrous post, dated 2011, and titled, Why software is eating the world.
In 2011, software was indeed eating the world. A new wave of digital pathfinders developed and launched innovative software that would inevitably take the internet by storm. We had a surge of companies such as Amazon, Hubspot, Mailchimp, Salesforce, and Pipedrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bespoke software - Build web apps with no code and for free</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/design/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BPM Software | Budibase is simple, free and open source</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/automate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/automate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Database application builder | Free - open source - no code</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/data/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Database Apps - The easy way to build database apps for free</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/deploy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Code Platform Pricing | Budibase</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/pricing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-hosting no code platform | Budibase</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/self-host/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/self-host/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budibase - made in Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/european-regional-development-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/european-regional-development-fund/</guid>
      <description>Budibase was founded in Belfast, Northern Ireland. We are proud to be part of such an amazing tech and business community.
One of the many amazing benefits of operating a business from Belfast, is having access to the European Regional Development Fund, via InvestNI.
We have been granted funds to employ local, highly skilled engineers to help build the Budibase builder and hosting platform.
Thank you InvestNI in recognising the huge, worldwide potential of Budibase to empower busineeses to build web apps, quickly and easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Backend Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/careers/senior-backend-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/careers/senior-backend-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Description Budibase is an open-source low code platform, designed for speed and customisation. When you need to build, launch, and grow a web application, Budibase has you covered. To date, we&amp;rsquo;ve received over 10,000 signups from the likes of F1, Deloitte, KPMG and we&amp;rsquo;re a few weeks from private beta. We have also recently secured a funding round and are seeking to expand our team in Belfast as we take our product to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior JavaScript Engineer</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/careers/full-stack-javascript-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/careers/full-stack-javascript-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Description Budibase is an open-source low code platform, designed for speed and customisation. When you need to build, launch, and grow a web application, Budibase has you covered. To date, we&amp;rsquo;ve received over 10,000 signups from the likes of F1, Deloitte, KPMG and we&amp;rsquo;re a few weeks from private beta. We have also recently secured a funding round and are seeking to expand our team in Belfast as we take our product to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 12 best no-code tools in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/no-code-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/no-code-tools/</guid>
      <description>No-code tools empower people around the world to build technology without code. Before no-code tools, building a simple web application was a challenging task, and often left to developers. Thankfully, this is not the case anymore. While no-code tools cannot solve all technical challenges, having the right no-code stack can undoubtedly help you get certain jobs done a lot faster, easier, and cheaper.
There are hundreds of no-code tools available, some free and some expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 web development tools you must know about in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-development-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-development-tools/</guid>
      <description>What does a doctor, builder, and developer have in common?
They are all highly skilled individuals who use tools to improve their workflow and do their jobs.
By now, developers recognize that web development tools play an integral role in the development process. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible to build a web application without them! (I&amp;rsquo;m happy to be proven wrong here.)
In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ve rounded up some of the most helpful tools for developing a successful web application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A beginners guide to web application development (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-application-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-application-development/</guid>
      <description>It was the year 2010, I had an idea for a web application which would allow my family and I to share images, organise shopping, populate a shared calendar, and store bills. My family was terribly disorganised. We needed this!
This idea was going to make me 💰💰💰.
There was a small complication with my vision - I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to build a web application. But thankfully, I could build a static site with HTML and CSS so it couldn&amp;rsquo;t be that hard, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Last updated January 01, 2019
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Budibase (“company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at joe@budibase.com.
When you visit our website and use our services, you trust us with your personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Code Investment - we are open to investment</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/investment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Recent Examples Of Modern Web Application Design (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/5-examples-of-web-application-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/5-examples-of-web-application-design/</guid>
      <description>Every once in a while, I&amp;rsquo;ll come across examples of web application design that really draw me in. I&amp;rsquo;ve listed these web applications below and ranked them from 5 - 1.
These web applications contain a beautiful mix of design, usability and creativity. They are masterpieces, and wonderful tokens of inspiration.
Huge amounts of time and thought have went into the design of these web applications and credit must go to the designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 8 Web App Ideas You&#39;ll Want To Steal (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-app-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-app-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Do you ever feel like the hardest part of building a web application is thinking of the idea?
You&amp;rsquo;re not alone.
Coming up with web app ideas consumes a lot of time.
Finding an idea which solves a problem, is possible to build, and won&amp;rsquo;t take millions of dollars is really difficult.
We get it.
Which is why we spent 3 weeks researching viable ideas to help you build a successful web app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a web app: A beginner&#39;s guide (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/how-to-make-a-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/how-to-make-a-web-app/</guid>
      <description>Picture by Med Badr
  In this post, I’m going to show you EXACTLY how to make a web app.
In fact, this is the process I’ve used, revised and perfected over the last 5 years.
I’ve used this exact process, or a version of it to build over 15 applications of all shapes and sizes. For me, this is 100% the best way to build web applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Good Habits For Success In 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/5-good-habits-for-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/5-good-habits-for-success/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m the cofounder of Budibase - a super speedy web app builder for makers.
Over the last 15 years working on small to large (£15m+) projects, I&amp;rsquo;ve often considered what is success, and what are the good habits for success in 2019.
I&amp;rsquo;ve poured my thoughts on to this page to help others in a similar position, develop successful habits.
I hope you enjoy it.
  Photo byDrew Beamer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank-you!</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/thankyou/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Web Apps Can Now Be Shipped Via The Play Store</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/progressive-web-app-play-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/progressive-web-app-play-store/</guid>
      <description>With Chrome 72, you can now publish your PWA in the Play Store and from the browser.
Chrome 72 was shipped in November 2018 and included Tursted Web Activity (TWA) which allows you to open Chrome in standalone mode thanks to your native Android package.
The primary advantages over your normal PWA installation are:
  Home screen widget
  Offer a wear OS companion app
  Background services can access native features</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budibase Core. A Serverless Database Engine, for fast SaaS development.</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/budibase-core-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/budibase-core-intro/</guid>
      <description>At Budibase, we are building a platform for accelerated development and easy management of SaaS businesses. We are beginning at the very bottom of the stack, by inventing a database engine specifically for this purpose. This post will attempt to give a good overview of what we are trying to achieve. I will get into detail in later posts.
What we need from a database A key requirement of Budibase is the ability to reduce repetition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Micro SaaS Ideas You&#39;ll Want To Steal in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/micro-saas-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/micro-saas-ideas/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m often thinking of Micro SaaS ideas for my next project but most of the time they are either rubbish or I don&amp;rsquo;t have the capacity to pursue them.
Instead of throwing all the good ideas away, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share them with you - how thoughtful, right 😄.
This post is not a simple static list; created, posted, and forgotten about. I will revisit and update this list on a monthly basis, delivering you super-fresh ideas to feed your entrepreneurial hunger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3 components of co-founder validation</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/cofoundervalidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/cofoundervalidation/</guid>
      <description>When someone whom you respect, approaches you with a business proposal, you listen. When their idea passes your gut validation, you get excited. When their vision of how a business should operate aligns with your vision, you fall in love with the product instantly. Your future brightens 💥
Respect, idea validation, shared vision. The 3 components of cofounder validation.
Respect can be earned, but best when it&amp;rsquo;s natural. Natural respect is only possible through previous encounters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Budibase | A software company specialising in no code</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Budibase - We try to respond within 2 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The wonderful people of Budibase</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budibase - The Fastest Way To Build A Web App For Free</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/build-a-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/build-a-web-app/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budibase - The Secure Choice For Web Application Hosting</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/host-a-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/host-a-web-app/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budibase - The Smart Way To Manage Users</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/manage-a-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/manage-a-web-app/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
