<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Build on Budibase: Web App Builder - Build Your Web App With Speed</title>
    <link>https://www.budibase.com/categories/build/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Build on Budibase: Web App Builder - Build Your Web App With Speed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed and owned by Budibase</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.budibase.com/categories/build/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>40 web development tools you must know about in 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-development-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-development-tools/</guid>
      <description>What does a doctor, builder, and developer have in common?
They are all highly skilled individuals who use tools to improve their workflow and do their jobs.
By now, developers recognize that web development tools play an integral role in the development process. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible to build a web application without them! (I&amp;rsquo;m happy to be proven wrong here.)
In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ve rounded up some of the most helpful tools for developing a successful web application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A beginners guide to web application development (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-application-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/web-application-development/</guid>
      <description>It was the year 2010, I had an idea for a web application which would allow my family and I to share images, organise shopping, populate a shared calendar, and store bills. My family was terribly disorganised. We needed this!
This idea was going to make me 💰💰💰.
There was a small complication with my vision - I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to build a web application. But thankfully, I could build a static site with HTML and CSS so it couldn&amp;rsquo;t be that hard, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a web app: A beginner&#39;s guide (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/how-to-make-a-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/how-to-make-a-web-app/</guid>
      <description>Picture by Med Badr
  In this post, I’m going to show you EXACTLY how to make a web app.
In fact, this is the process I’ve used, revised and perfected over the last 5 years.
I’ve used this exact process, or a version of it to build over 15 applications of all shapes and sizes. For me, this is 100% the best way to build web applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Web Apps Can Now Be Shipped Via The Play Store</title>
      <link>https://www.budibase.com/blog/progressive-web-app-play-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.budibase.com/blog/progressive-web-app-play-store/</guid>
      <description>With Chrome 72, you can now publish your PWA in the Play Store and from the browser.
Chrome 72 was shipped in November 2018 and included Tursted Web Activity (TWA) which allows you to open Chrome in standalone mode thanks to your native Android package.
The primary advantages over your normal PWA installation are:
  Home screen widget
  Offer a wear OS companion app
  Background services can access native features</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>